export default {
    name: "Animals",
    description: "A card deck containing basic animal vocabulary.",
    author: "aasd24",
    data: [
        {   
            id: crypto.randomUUID(),
            front: "🐘",
            back: "elephant",
        },
        {
            id: crypto.randomUUID(),
            front: "🦒",
            back: "giraffe",
        },
        {
            id: crypto.randomUUID(),
            front: "🦜",
            back: "parrot",
        },
        {
            id: crypto.randomUUID(),
            front: "🐱",
            back: "cat",
        },
        {
            id: crypto.randomUUID(),
            front: "🐶",
            back: "dog",
        },
        {
            id: crypto.randomUUID(),
            front: "🐭",
            back: "mouse",
        },
        {
            id: crypto.randomUUID(),
            front: "🦑",
            back: "squid",
        },
        {
            id: crypto.randomUUID(),
            front: "🦛",
            back: "hippo",
        },
        {
            id: crypto.randomUUID(),
            front: "🐷",
            back: "pig",
        },
        {
            id: crypto.randomUUID(),
            front: "🐀",
            back: "rat",
        },
    ]
}
    